<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>List of Publications on Guillaume Coiffier - Personal Website</title>
    <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in List of Publications on Guillaume Coiffier - Personal Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1-Lipschitz Neural Distance Fields</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/onelipsdf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/onelipsdf/</guid>
      <description>Signed Distance Function This work aims at computing good quality implicit representation of implicit objects. Instead of relying on discrete structures like point clouds, voxel grid or meshes to represent a geometrical object, those representations define surface and curves as the level set (usually the zero level set) of some function. Among the infinity of continuous functions that can implicitly represent a given an object $\Omega \subset \mathbb{R}^n$, the one that best preserves the properties of $\Omega$ far from its zero level set is the Signed Distance Function (SDF) of $\Omega$, which is defined as:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD Thesis: Global Parametrization Algorithms for Quadmeshing</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/phd_thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/phd_thesis/</guid>
      <description>This work was supervised by Dmitry Sokolov and Etienne Corman.
The defense occurred on December 6th 2023 at the Université de Lorraine.
Jury  Xavier Goaoc, Université de Lorraine [President] Mirela Ben-Chen, Technion Israel Institute of Technology [Reviewer] Marco Tarini, University of Milan [Reviewer] Bruno Lévy, Inria, Centre de l&amp;rsquo;Université de Lorraine Pooran Memari, CNRS, Ecole Polytechnique Mélina Skouras, Inria, Centre de l&amp;rsquo;Université de Grenoble Etienne Corman, CNRS, LORIA [Advisor] Dmitry Sokolov, Université de Lorraine [Advisor]  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Method of Moving Frames for Surface Parametrization</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/moving_frames/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/moving_frames/</guid>
      <description>Quadmeshing with Seamless Parametrization Computing a high-quality quadmesh of a given object is a challenging task of geometry processing, with applications in both computer graphics and numerical simulation. A promising approach to solve this problem is to rely on a parametrization, that is a flat representation of the considered object. The idea is to overlay a grid on this parametrization which will then be pulled back onto the surface to form the quad layout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robust One-Class Classification with Signed Distance Function using 1-Lipschitz Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/occsdf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/occsdf/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parametric Surface Fitting on Airborne Lidar Point Clouds for Building Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/roofit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/roofit/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ThriftyNets: Convolutional Neural Networks With Tiny Parameter Budget</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/thriftynet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/thriftynet/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Geological Image Synthesis from 2D Examples using Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/diagan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/publications/diagan/</guid>
      <description>A preliminary version of this work was presented at the Petroleum Geostatistics Conference in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
