<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cvs on Guillaume Coiffier - Personal Website</title>
    <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cvs on Guillaume Coiffier - Personal Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/info/</guid>
      <description>Since November 2025, I am a permanent Inria researcher in Grenoble (France). I work in the CRAFT research group, which studies the computationnal design and fabrication of objects with mechanical functions.&#xA;From 2024 to September 2025, I was a post-doc at the Catholic University of Louvain in Louvain-la-Neuve (Belgium), where I worked on injective deformation of meshes in the context of the X-mesh project.&#xA;I obtained a PhD from the University of Lorraine under the supervision of Etienne Corman and Dmitry Sokolov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Current and past positions</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/positions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/positions/</guid>
      <description>[Since Nov. 2025] Permanent Researcher (&amp;ldquo;Chargé de recherche&amp;rdquo;)&#xA;Inria, Grenoble Alpes University, Montbonnot Saint-Martin, France&#xA;CRAFT research team: computationnal design of objects with mechanical functions.&#xA;[Jan. 2024 - Sep. 2025] Post-doc / Research Assistant&#xA;Université Catholique de Louvain, Louvain-la-Neuve, Belgium&#xA;Meshing sharp physical interfaces in finite element simulation&#xA;Member of the X-mesh team lead by Jean-François Remacle and Nicolas Moës&#xA;[Sep. 2020 - Dec. 2023] PhD Student&#xA;LORIA, University of Lorraine, Nancy, France</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/education/</guid>
      <description>[2020-2023] PhD, Global Parametrization Algorithms for Quadmeshing &amp;ndash; LORIA, Université de Lorraine, Nancy, France &amp;ndash; Under the supervision of Dmitry Sokolov and Etienne Corman&#xA;[2016-2020] Ms Student in Computer Science &amp;ndash; École Normale Supérieure de Lyon, Lyon, France&#xA;[2013-2016] French &amp;ldquo;Preparatory classes&amp;rdquo;, Mathematics-Physics-Computer Science &amp;ndash; Lycée Henri Wallon, Valenciennes, France</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conferences, Seminars and Workshops</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/talks/</guid>
      <description>International conferences The Method of Moving Frames for Surface Global Parametrization SIGGRAPH 2024&#xA;1-Lipschitz Neural Distance Fields, Symposium on Geometry Processing 2024 [Video]&#xA;:trophy: Best Paper Award&#xA;3D Geological Image Synthesis from 2D Examples Using Generative Adversarial Networks, Petroleum Geostatistics 2019 [Abstract]&#xA;National (French) conferences and workshops Robust Neural Distance Fields using 1-Lipschitz Neural Networks, Rencontres des jeunes chercheurs du groupe de travail en modélisation géométrique, Marseille, 27 mars 2024 [Slides]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/publications/</guid>
      <description>See the list of publications or Google Scholar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/teaching/</guid>
      <description>[2024-2025] Lecturer, École Polytechnique de Louvain Computational Geometry (LMECA2170) [Slides] [2022-2023] Teaching Assistant, École des Mines de Nancy Programmation and Data Structures Operational Research Algorithms and Complexity [2020-2022] Teaching Assistant, Faculty of Sciences and Technology, Nancy, France Algorithms and programmation in Python Coding Project: Video game in C Automata, Grammars and Languages Optimization, Operational Research [2018-2021] Advisor for the boot camp Girls Can Code!, Lyon, France </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular Science</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/mediation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/mediation/</guid>
      <description>I take part in Inria&amp;rsquo;s program Chiche! whose goal is to make each French high school student meet a computer scientist. With this program, I&amp;rsquo;ve met a dozen of classes in high schools of eastern France between 2021 and 2023.&#xA;In 2022, I participated in the international French-speaking contest of popular science Ma thèse en 180 secondes, where I got the second best prize of the University of Lorraine for my talk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awards</title>
      <link>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GCoiffier.github.io/cv/awards/</guid>
      <description>Best paper award for 1-Lipschitz Neural Distance Fields, Symposium on Geometry Processing, 2024&#xA;2nd best paper for Ajustement de surfaces paramétriques sur nuages de points (Video), JFIG 2021</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
